Guide to the Jody Fischer Collection of Willie Nelson
The Wittliff Collections
Jody Fischer Collection of Willie Nelson
1976-2003
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Fischer, Jody
SWWC.103
14 Linear Feet
22 boxes
Jody Fischer's collection of photographs, audio cassette tapes and VHS tapes relating to Willie Nelson. The materials are arranged into the following six series: Personal Papers, Ephemera, Photographs, Audio Cassette Tapes, VHS Tapes, and T-Shirts and Hats.
Scope and Contents
The Jody Fischer Collection of Willie Nelson spans from 1976-2003, with the bulk of the materials covering 1983-1988. The collection is comprised of photographs, audio cassette tapes and video tapes collected by Jody Fischer that relate to Willie Nelson. The arrangement of the collection is entirely artificial as the materials were not organized when received. Titles in quotation marks were written by Jody Fischer.
The collection is arranged into the following six series: Personal Papers, Ephemera, Photographs, Audio Cassette Tapes, VHS Tapes, and T-Shirts and Hats.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jody Fischer.
Related Materials
Some previous material related to Willie Nelson donated by Fischer is located in the SWWC Collection 021, The Willie Nelson Collection.
Biographical Notes
There is not a lot of information available about Jody Fischer. She was born December 21, 1949. During the 1970's she lived in New York City where she was active with the music scene. She was a musician and writer herself. According to a 1991 Texas Monthly article, she started following Willie Nelson in the early 1970's helping wherever she could. When he purchased the Pedernales Country Club in 1979, she was hired on as his personal secretary. Her job was to schedule studio time for Willie and his musician friends, assist Lana Nelson with charitable work, and generally assist in managing the property. She also had a small part in his movie, the Red-Headed Stranger, which was filmed on the property.
When Willie Nelson began the Farm Aid movement, Jody took calls coming in from famers and their families, and is often quoted as being a compassionate listener. She was very close to the extended Nelson family, as well as involved in diverse causes such as Farm Aid and Native American civil rights.
Jody passed away on December 25, 2003, at the Christopher House hospice for cancer patients, in the Willie Nelson room.
Index Terms
Subjects
Country music; Concerts; Musicians -- Texas; Motion pictures -- Production and direction; Rock music
Document Types
Photographs
Subjects (Persons)
Nelson, Willie, 1933-; William D. Wittliff
Subjects (Corporations)
Farm Aid (Fund raising enterprise)
- Personal Papers, 1985-1986, 2003, undated
  Series Description
  This series includes correspondence letters, rough drafts of song lyrics and a birthday card to Jody Fischer.
  - "Jody Fischer: Celebration of Life." Program and printouts of photographs, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Contents
    Letter to Jody Fischer from Don Mischer, undated
    Birthday card to Jody Fischer from Connie Nelson, [1985]
    Letter to Willie Nelson from Gary Fiellgaard. Handwritten lyrics to "She Can Survive" on yellow notebook paper enclosed.
    Pedernales Recording Studio letterhead and envelope (blank)
    Map of Ned Blessing locations by Lauren Film Productions
  - Lyrics by Kris Kristofferson - "El Gavilan," "The Heart, " "Mean Old Man" (handwriting unidentified), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings about Willie Nelson (3) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ephemera, 1977, 1985-1987, undated
  This series includes programs, a calendar, and a press kit for Red Headed Stranger. The press kit includes photos on set, director's notes and cast descriptions. Programs include Austin Opry House performances, Run for Your Life program, Farm Aid 1985 program and First Decade Reunion program. The calendar is a Willie Nelson calendar from 1983.
  - Programs, 1977, 1985-1987
    - "Austin Opry House welcomes you to Rusty Weir with the Howlers", September 9-10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Austin Opry House welcomes you to Willie Nelson & Family" [featuring Bobbie Nelson and Pop Nelson], October 14, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - First Decade Reunion program with envelope, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Willie Nelson discography, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Willie Nelson and Family", undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Program for the first Farm Aid in Champaign, Illinois, September 22, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Run for your life: A benefit for cancer research" (Jody Fischer is listed in the special thanks), undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Press Kit for Red Headed Stranger - Programs (4), Notes, Publicity Stills (6), Cast descriptions (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Photographs, 1984-1988
  This series is divided into six parts: Willie Nelson portraits; Willie Nelson performing; Willie Nelson with others [non-performance]; non-Willie Nelson photographs; snapshots on the set of Red Headed Stranger, and snapshots on the set of Ned Blessing.
  - Willie Nelson Portraits, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Wearing red bandana
    Driving a pickup truck (2)
    Speaking
    Standing next to a pickup on a snowy day
    Wearing leopard print "punk Willie"
    Shirtless with new haircut
    Wearing black hat
  - Sketch, undated (Map-case Dr 24)
  - Willie Nelson Performing, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    With Belles of Joy in studio (5)
    In back room of Pedernales Recording Studio
    With others in recording studio (2)
    With Ray Charles recording (5)
    On stage alone
    Fourth of July concert (2)
    Farm Aid (5)
    With Neil Young and John Mellencamp at Farm Aid
    With Johnny Cash at Farm Aid
  - Willie Nelson playing guitar in front of a bus, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Willie Nelson with Others [non performance], 1986, 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    George Jones
    Jody Fischer, Sammy Allred at Lone Star album release
    Lana Nelson's wedding, August 8, 1988
    Neil Young on "Working Cowboys" video (5)
    Merle Haggard, David Lyn Jones
    Faran Young, Fred Foster
    Jesse Jackson at Farm Aid (2)
    Jody Fischer, Fred Foster, Faran Young, Chip Young, Bobby Arnold
    Playing golf (2)
    Driving with a passenger
    Others on set of "Red Headed Stranger" (10)
    B Spears on set of "Red Headed Stranger"
    Crew of "Red Headed Stranger" filming (16)
    Jody Fischer, Carolyn Mugar, Bill Wittliff, Lana Nelson at Wittliff's office, 1986. (Photo by Bill Wittliff)
  - Willie Nelson and Kris Kristofferson (3-1 framed), undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Non-Willie Nelson Photographs (1 of 3), 1986, 1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    IRS auction pictures (3)
    Carolyn Mugar, Bill Wittliff, Jody Fischer, Manc Rothbaum at Tuscan January, 1986 (10)
    Wittliff, Fischer, Drascoll, Roach at "Ned Blessing" wrap
    Bill Wittliff and Connie Todd at work (2)
    Bill Wittliff and Jody Fischer on set
    Tim Scott and Jody Fischer on set
    Hank Snow, Johnny Gimble on couch
    Carolyn Mugar and Jody Fischer at Red Headed Stranger opening
    Coach Royal, Bill McDavid, Booker T. Jones, Bobby Arnold, Larry Greenhill, Jody Fischer- live performance at Cowboys game
    Booker T. Jones and Larry Greenhill- "Without a Song" session
    Chips Mamam at Willie Nelson's studio
    Bobby Emmens, Davis Cherry, Reggie Young, Larry Greenhill, Bobby Arnold, Mike Lach- "Memphis Band" taking a break
    Jody Fischer, Larry Greenhill, Bobby Arnold, Lana Nelson- Pedernales Recording Studio staff
    Bobby Arnold, Ray Benson, Freddy Powers- singing in back room of Pedernales Studio
    Townes Van Zandt on set of "Pancho and Lefty" (3)
    Carolyn Mugar and Jody Fischer on Willie Nelson's boat
    Kimmie Rhodes and Bobby Lee Nelson
    Kimmie Rhodes and Joe Ely
    Lana Nelson standing by red car
    Connie Todd posing for camera
    Connie Todd, Lana Nelson, Luis Avalos, Jody Fischer on set of Ned Blessing
    Larry Greenhill and Bobby Arnold as "golf kings"
    Bobbie Nelson and Clifford Antone at Lana Nelson's wedding, August 8, 1988
  - Non-Willie Nelson photographs (2 of 3), undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Jody Fischer and Kris Kristofferson (4)
    Carolyn Mugar at work (2)
    Cast and Crew down on set (11)
    Luck, TX on a snowy day
    View of River (2)
    Pedernales Recording Studio- control room
    Lana Nelson in Jody Fischer's office at Pedernales Recording Studio (4)
    Farm Aid donation box
  - Non-Willie Nelson photographs - Negatives (3 of 3), undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Snapshots on the set of Red Headed Stranger (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    Willie Nelson (39)
    Bill Wittliff (5)
    Morgan Fairchild (1)
    General (98)
  - Snapshots on the set of Ned Blessing (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Willie Nelson (1)
    Jody Fischer (22)
    General (52)
- Posters, undated
  Posters are divided into Willie Nelson and non-Willie Nelson subseries. The Nelson posters include ones for the sixth annual Fourth of July picnic; Honeysuckle Rose, and two advertising concerts. The bulk of the non-Willie Nelson posters are for concerts at the Austin Opry House by performers such as The Charlie Daniels Band, Kinky Friedman, Dave Loggins, The Lost Gonzo Band, and Taj Mahal.
  - Willie Nelson Posters, 1978-1979, 1984, 2000
    - Willie Nelson's Sixth Annual Fourth of July Picnic. Austin Opry House. Poster by Danny Garrett, July 3-4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Honeysuckle Rose starring Willie Nelson as Buck Bonham. Hemisfair Arena. Also featuring Dyan Cannon, Amy Irving, Slim Pickens, Mickey Rooney [filming concert for movie], October 10, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Second Annual Alaska Airlines Willie Nelson Concert, George Sullivan Arena, Anchorage, Alaska, February 6-7, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Willie Nelson, The Honkey-Tonk Hero, Live. [Zetner], 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Other Posters, 1977-1984
    - The Charlie Daniels Band. Austin Opry House. Poster by [Danny] Garrett [2 copies; slightly different colors], June 30-July 1, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Desert Dance Benefit. Featuring Lost Gonzo Band, Beto & the Fairlanes, Mother of Pearl, Bobby Bridger, Butch Hancock, Jurt Van Sickle, Natalie Zoe and Turk Pipkin & Kim. Austin Opera House. Poster by Bert Goodrich, November 12, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Kinky Friedman and the Texas Jewboys, The Lost Gonzo Band, Paul Ray and the X-Rated Cobras. Austin Opry House. Poster by Michael Priest, October 31, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival. Featuring Marcia Ball, Guy Clark, Alvin Crow, Steven Fromholz, Nanci Griffith, Ray Wiley Hubbard, Gary P. Nunn, Willis Alan Ramsey, B. W. Stevenson, Townes Van Zandt, Rusty Weir, and more. [Festival information on reverse side of poster], May 24-28, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Dave Loggins & Kiwi Austin Opry House. Poster by Danny Garrett., February 5, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Lost Gonzo Band, "Benefit of the Doubt: A Reunion," with Gary P. Nunn, Robert Livingston, John Inmon, Paul Pearcy, Jerry Jeff Walker, and Ray Wylie Hubbard. Armadillo. Poster by [Danny] Garrett, February 7, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Taj Mahal. Austin Opry House. Poster by Danny Garrett, November 24, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Michael Murphey. Gregory Gym [University of Texas Homecoming], October 19, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Official Quarterhorse Racing. Manor Downs Poster by Michael Priest, March 18-25, April 22-23, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Sea Level and Texoid. Austin Opry House. Flyer by Wilkins/Calico., December 8, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Texas Country Music Sings for the Runaway Hotline. Austin Opera House. Featuring Michael Martin Murphey, Jerry Jeff Walker, Gary P. Nunn, Ray Wiley Hubbard, B. W. Stevenson, Rusty Wier, Bobby Bridger, Geezinslaws, Lost Gonzo Reunion, and Steve Fromholz as emcee. Poster by Jim Franklin, October 5, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Tom Waits with Jonnie Barnett. Austin Opry House. Poster by Pauline Walsh Fernandes., November 12, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Jerry Jeff Walker with Joe Ely. Austin Opry House, August 26-27, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Rusty Wier and Backbone. Austin Opry House. Poster by Wilkins, March 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Jesse Winchester. Austin Opry House. Poster by [Danny] Garrett, August 30, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Warren Zevon. Austin Opry House. Poster by [Danny] Garrett, June 2, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Shotgun Productions "Presents the Reunion of The Cherokee Cowboys" poster, undated (Map-case Dr 24)
    - "Being Country, Tom T. Hall vs. Joe Ely" sketch, undated (Map-case Dr 24)
- Audio Cassette Tapes, 1976-1995
  These audio cassettes primarily feature Willie Nelson, though there are several of other recording artists. The cassettes are in varying condition, some have been recorded over multiple times and the labels are not always descriptive of what is on the tape. The series of audio recordings has been divided into 5 subseries; Jody Fischer recordings, Willie Nelson studio recordings, Willie Nelson dated live recordings, Willie Nelson undated live recordings, and other recording artists. The collection also included a variety of commercially produced and released cassettes that have been transferred to the library holdings.
  The cassettes covered a broad scope of music, as well as some personal recordings of events, phone calls and jam sessions. The cassettes did not have a particular original order, and when possible have been arranged by date. The priority for sorting recordings was broken down by separating out the Studio recordings, Jody's own recordings which give insight to the interests and activities outside of strictly music that she participated in as an individual and as Willie Nelson's personal assistant. Following that recordings are sorted by those including Willie Nelson, and those of other artists.
  When it is not possible to sort by date, the recordings are sorted by alphabetical order of contributing artists. Often the labels only include first names, such as Hank, Dolly, Kris, Frank, and Johnny to name a few. While some of the last names can be inferred based on other famous musicians and context, last names that have been added by the processing staff are put in parenthesis to indicate that they are additions not included on the actual labels. Subseries 1: Jody Fisher Recordings, 1988-1996, undated These recordings are difficult to date, frequently Fischer has recorded over other tapes, and many of her recordings have Willie Nelson music on the other side. These recordings include phone conversations, Hawaiian music taped from the radio on her trip to Hawaii, and programs focusing on Native American civil rights, amongst other topics. Subseries 2: Willie Nelson Studio Recordings, 1983-1987, undated These recordings with one exception are from the Pedernales Studio. They are arranged by date when possible, with undated recordings at the end of the series.
  Subseries 3: Willie Nelson Recordings Dated, 1976-1995 These recordings vary from jam sessions to concerts to rough recordings prior to production. Often they include other artists such as Kris Kristofferson, Merle Haggard, and other country, folk and blues artists.
  Subseries 4: Willie Nelson Recordings, Undated These recordings are similar to those in subseries 3, except that they are undated. Recordings will be grouped by collaborating artists listed on the labels.
  Subseries 5: Recordings by Other Artists, 1982-1986, undated These are other unproduced recordings in the Jody Fischer collections featuring other artists. These are sorted alphabetically by artist last name.
  - Jody Fischer Tapes, 1988-1996, undated
    - "Bob Fall – 88" (written in red over previously labeled Half Nelson) This is an audio recording of phone conversations between Jody and someone named Bob. The conversations range over a variety of topics such as attending a Native American Sundance, the "Lakota Times" newspaper, Eagle Butte and Kansas City, a Farm Aid meeting in Boston and a trip to Maui in September with Willie Nelson, 1988 (Box 4)
    - "1/11/1990 Jody/KILI Radio" Recording of Jody Addressing the Leaders of the Lakota Nation addressing support for Sundances, support for grass roots workers, questions about leadership priorities and spiritual practices. The other side of the recording is Willie Nelson Music, January 11, 1990 (Box 4)
    - "Jam Session – Rachel, Lana, Jody, Mike, Larry" Recording is of poor sound quality or has deteriorated, hard to hear. Opposite side is a recording of "Willie and Bobby Lee, September 13, 1996 (Box 4)
    - "Picnic" This cassette is hard to categorize. There are multiple voices talking, one sounds like Jody. There are discussions of spirit guides and angelic hosts and some visualization/meditation exercises., undated (Box 4)
    - "A) John Trudell 7A6 Interview Outlaws for Peace" Recording of an interview with references to Jody Fischer and "B) Tom & Loretta Cook Michael H Melvin Lee Many Horses" which is a talk about Indian Reservations, rights, and religious freedoms., undated (Box 4)
    - "Kaleo – Kalani Never, Never, Never/ Melvin (unintelligible)" other side "Hawaiian" This was recorded off of a Hawaiian radio station, likely during her vacation on Maui in the late 80's, undated (Box 4)
    - "KRTR – un-rock Hawaiian" also recorded from the radio in Hawaii, undated (Box 4)
  - Willie Nelson Studio Recordings, 1983-1987, undated
    - Tape labeled "Willie- Ruffs" Pedernales Studio, April 18, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Without a song" Pedernales Studio (copy) A Side: Golden Earrings, To Each His Own, Harbor Lights, Once in a While, As Time Goes By, Without a Song, I Can't Begin to Tell You B Side: Autumn Leaves, You'll Never Know, Dreamer's Holiday, July 13, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Julio & Willie As Time Goes" Pedernales Studio. Written on tape: "To All the Girls, As Time Goes By, To All the Girls (video)", July 28, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Songwriter #2" Pedernales Studio (copy) A Side: Will She Take the Love, Down to Her Socks, Night to Remember B Side: Night to Remember, Who Am I, Sure Could be Sweet, December 8, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Songwriter #3" Pedernales Studio (copy) A Side: Sure Could be Sweet, The Show Goes On B Side: One for the Morning, Late Again, Great Balls of Fire, I'm a Goin' Fishin', Lay me Down, Forever in Your Love, The Wonder, If it's all the Same, December 14, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Nelson & Jackie King" Pedernales Studio (copy) A Side: Thank You, Keep on Playing the Music, I Fall in Love too Easy, Angel Eyes B Side: My Window Faces South, Heart of a Clown, Jealous Heart, There Will Never be Another You, January 31, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie and…Tape #1" Pederales Studio "Neil Young, Leon Russel, Ray Charles, Robert Duvall, Johnny Rodriguez", July 25, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie & Hank (Snow) Ruffs" Pedernales Studio "Brand On my Heart, Now & Then, Send me the Pillow, I Don't Hurt Anymore, Golden Rocket, I've Been Everywhere, I'm Moving On, Makes No Difference Now, Trouble Carebbean" (sic), September 29, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie & Family Ruffs" Pedernales Studio Side A: Forgiving You Was Easy, I Let My Mind Wander, I'm a Memory, She's Gone, I Never Cared for You, You Wouldn't Cross the Street, Me + Paul, One Day at a Time, Pretend I Never Happened, On a Fast Train, November 29, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie & Merle Ruff Mixes", November 30, 1985 (Box 4)
      Tape has a date of December 1, 1985 on label.
    - "Willie Nelson & Paul Buskirk" Pedernales Studio Side A: Everywhere You Go, Sophisticated Lady, Afraid, Dark Town Strutter's Ball, You Always Hurt the One You Love, Greensleeve, I'll Keep on Loving You, Linda, Dardella, Lola, Nacogdoches Waltz, Under Paris Skies, December Day, Moonlight becomes You Side B: Intermezzo, The World is Waiting For Sunrise, Joy, Little Rock Get Away, Banjo Sons, October 1986 (Box 4)
    - "Willie – Mix" Pedernales Studio (copy) Side A: Island in the Sea, Don't Wake Me, Little Things, Last Thing on my Mind, There is no Easy way, Nobody There but Me, Cold Nov. (sic) Wind, Women Who Love Too Much Side B: All in the Name of Love, Sky Train, May 1987 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Nelson – Ruffs" Pedernales Studio (copy) Still, Still Moving Me, No Tear Drops Tonight, Wedding Bells, Milk Cow Blues, Philadelphia Lawyer, Go Home with the Girls, Try Me One More Time, Walking the Floor Over You, House of Blue Lights, Leaving's Not the Only Way to Go, Trifle on Ya, So Lonesome I Could Cry, September 11, 1987 (Box 4)
    - "Willie & Faron" Pedernales Studio Side A. (notated as Ruff Mix) Hello Halls, Congratulations, Funny How Time Slips Away, Touch Me, Sweet Dreams, Three Days Side B. Half a Man, Live Fast, Love Hard, Die Young, Forgeting (sic) Seems to Take the Longest Time, Going Steady, Four in the Morning, Life Turned Her That Way, She's Not For You, undated (Box 4)
    - "Willie Nelson & Jackie King" Woodland Sound Studios Nashville, TN, undated (Box 4)
    - "Seven Spanish Angels" Pedernales Studio (Tape is damaged), undated (Box 4)
  - Willie Nelson Recordings Dated, 1976-1995
    - "Willie Nelson – Circle Star Theater 3/5/76 San Carlos, Calif", March 5, 1976 (Box 4)
    - "Willie + Jackie – Wexler" (likely Jackie King, a guitar player), January 27, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Old Ways" (a Neil Young album featuring Willie Nelson), January 29, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Merle, Willie, Freddy, Dean" (possibly Freddy Powers and Dean Reynolds), April 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Who'll Buy My Memories" (damaged), August 8, 1983 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Nelson/Robert Duvall", July 16, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Kathleen/Wally, etc. Willie", July 17, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Nelson & Family Ruffs", December 16, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Ruffs", September 29, 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Willie & Hank" (Hank Snow), 1984 (Box 4)
    - "Neil Young with Willie Sandstone", August 24, 1985 (Box 4)
    - "Willie Ruffs", December 20, 1985 (Box 4)
    - "WN+F Jacksonville", May 9, 1986 (Box 4)
    - "A) Willie + Gary B) Master Second Ten (blank)", June 11, 1986 (Box 4)
    - "Women Who Love Too Much, All in the Name of Love, Sky Train Willie & Booker" (Other side: "#550 Whose Land?" Part IV The American Lutheran Church Media Services Center 1568 Eustis Street St. Paul, MN 55100), July 1986, undated (Box 4)
    - "Willie – Christmas", December 6, 1987 (Box 5)
    - "House Called Music Willie", April 1989 (Box 5)
    - "Willie" (cassette liner has handwritten note "I get thru the days by thinking of when I'll be with you"), October 17, 1989 (Box 5)
    - "A Just One Love", January 1990 (Box 5)
    - "Bobbie Lee & Willie", April 1990 (Box 5)
    - "Willie", November 10, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Willie Nelson Recordings, undated
    - A) "America No Vocals" B) "America with Vocal", undated (Box 5)
    - "The Band – Willie Nelson", undated (Box 5)
    - "Willie - Borderline" (starts off with Willie singing a Simon and Garfunkel song), undated (Box 5)
    - "City of New Orleans" and "Assorted Willie", undated (Box 5)
    - A side labeled "City of New Orleans" Side B labeled "Big Mike Management 408 W. 155 St. 2W NYC 10025" (has more Willie Nelson), undated (Box 5)
    - "Willie Concert" (damaged), undated (Box 5)
    - "The Hungry Years", undated (Box 5)
    - "Island in the Sea Willie Nelson" Other side labeled "Jim Bechtol" (Both sides seem to be Willie Nelson), undated (Box 5)
    - "No Place But Texas, I'm Not Trying to Forget You Anymore – Willie", undated (Box 5)
    - "Willie Nelson Old Tunes", undated (Box 5)
    - "Red Headed Stranger Sound in Your Mind", undated (Box 5)
    - "Willie Romance", undated (Box 5)